eslbuzz.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy - ESLBuzz Learning English

**Privacy Policy**

ESLBuzz.com (“ESLBuzz”) takes the private nature of your personal information very seriously.

This privacy policy, which we adapted from a policy originally provided by  _Automattic_  ([WordPress.com](https://wordpress.com/)), describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit and use our websites. Please read this notice very carefully.

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, ESLBuzz collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. ESLBuzz’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how ESLBuzz’s visitors use its website. From time to time, ESLBuzz may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g. by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

ESLBuzz also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. ESLBuzz does not use such information to identify its visitors, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to ESLBuzz’s websites choose to interact with ESLBuzz in ways that require ESLBuzz to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that ESLBuzz gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for ESLBuzz.com to provide a username and email address. In each case, ESLBuzz collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with ESLBuzz. ESLBuzz does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**

ESLBuzz may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, ESLBuzz may monitor the most popular collections on ESLBuzz.com. ESLBuzz may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, ESLBuzz does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. ESLBuzz uses cookies to help ESLBuzz identify and track visitors, their usage of ESLBuzz websites, and their website access preferences. ESLBuzz visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using ESLBuzz’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of ESLBuzz’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Ads**

Ads appearing on any ESLBuzz websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by ESLBuzz and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Links to Third Party  Sites**

This privacy policy only applies to information collected by ESLBuzz. This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that ESLBuzz does not own or control, or employees that ESLBuzz does not manage. A ESLBuzz website may contain links to third party websites. Any information you provide to, or that is collected by, third-party sites may be subject to the privacy policies of those sites, if any. We encourage you to read such privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your personally-identifying information, and ESLBuzz and its affiliates shall not be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your personally-identifying information by any third party.

**Security**

All non-personally-identifying information, potentially personally-identifying and personally identifying-information described above is stored on restricted database servers.

**Privacy Policy  Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, ESLBuzz may change its privacy policy from time to time, and in ESLBuzz’s sole discretion. ESLBuzz encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its privacy policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our sites in general, please [ _contact us_](https://www.eslbuzz.com/contact/).
